Finding Aid for Men's Glee Club (University of Michigan) records 1886-2012
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Sound Recordings
  - Reel-to-Reel Tapes
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club Annual Spring Concert, 1970 April 3; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch
      - [Tape 1, Part 1-2], [87250-SR-48-1-1-2]; mp3 file; (The Michigan Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Dona Nobis Pacem; Emmitte Spiritum; The Lord is My Light; Chorus of the Returning Pilgrims; Impatience; As Beautiful As She; I Love My Love; Five Nature Studies - The Urge; The Scripts Are Ready; A True Portend; Time To Sleep; The Discovery; If Ever I Would Leave You; Elijah; Were You There; Good News; Everytime I Feel The Spirit; Pollution; Wichita Lineman; MacArthur Park; What the World Needs Now; 'Tis of Michigan We Sing; A Toast to Michigan; I Wanna Go Back to Michigan; Drink, Drink, Joy Rules the Day; The Bum Army; Goddess of the Inland Seas; Michigan Men; The Old Friars' Song; Varsity and the Victors; Yellow and The Blue.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club "Michigan Songs", 1970 January 07; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Part 1], [87250-SR-49-1-1]; mp3 file; (The Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Michigan Medley; Goddess of the Inland Seas; Go Blue; Michigan Men; I'll Ne'er Forget My College Days; Drink! Drink! Joy Rules the Day; The University; Hymn to Michigan; Bum Army; Old Friar's Song; When Night Falls; Ann Arbor Days; Varsity; The Victors; The Yellow and Blue.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club - Studio Showcase, 1968 January 10; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Part 1], [87250-SR-50-1-1]; mp3 file; (The University of Michigan Men's Glee Club performing unlisted songs.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club in Luxembourg, 1971; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch
      - [Part 1], [87250-SR-51-1-1]; mp3 file; (The Men's Glee Club in Luxembourg, 1971. Recorded at Grand Studio Radio-Tele. Concert 2 VIII.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club in Japan, 1965 October 06; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-52-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; Men's Glee Club from concert given on October 6, 1965 Kwansei Gakuin Glee Club; dubbed 1971 March 20.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-52-2-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; Men's Glee Club from concert given on October 6, 1965 Kwansei Gakuin Glee Club; dubbed 1971 March 20.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club in Japan, 1971 March 20; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-52-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; Men's Glee Club from concert given on October 6, 1965 Kwansei Gakuin Glee Club; dubbed 1971 March 20. (Tape 1 not digitized)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club Luxembourg and Wales, 1971 July 11; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1-1], [87250-SR-53-1-1-1]; mp3 file; (U of M Glee Club Concert in Luxembourg.)
      - [Tape 1, Part 1-2], [87250-SR-53-1-1-2]; mp3 file; (U of M Glee Club Concert in Luxembourg.)
      - [Tape 1, Part 2-1], [87250-SR-53-1-2-1]; mp3 file; (Competition and Adjudication at Llangolleneisteddfod, Llangollen, Wales; Wayne State Glee Club Michigan's Glee Club, and Oral Adjudication.)
      - [Tape 1, Part 2-2], [87250-SR-53-1-2-2]; mp3 file; (Competition and Adjudication at Llangolleneisteddfod, Llangollen, Wales; Wayne State Glee Club Michigan's Glee Club, and Oral Adjudication.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club - WUOM, 1971 November 06; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Part 1], [87250-SR-54-1-1]; mp3 file; (WUOM recording of Men's Glee Club performing a selection of songs at Hill Auditorium, including selections by the Friars.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club, 1972 March 24; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch
      - [Tape 1, Part 1-1], [87250-SR-55-1-1-1]; mp3 file; (The Men's Glee Club performing at Hill Auditorium on March 24, 1972.)
      - [Tape 1, Part 1-2], [87250-SR-55-1-1-2]; mp3 file; (The Men's Glee Club performing at Hill Auditorium on March 24, 1972.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club Annual Spring Concert, 1972 March 25; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1-1], [87250-SR-56-1-1-1]; mp3 file; (The Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Surely He Hath Borne Our Griefs; Wir Eilen; Two Settings of a Poem by Rosaline; Festgesong an die Kunstler. Selections by the Friars: The Ballad of Little Musgrave and Lady Barnard; In His Care-O; Yonder Come Day; We've Only Just Begun; Spinning Wheel; Michigan Songs; Alma Mater.)
      - [Tape 1, Part 1-2], [87250-SR-56-1-1-2]; mp3 file; (The Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Surely He Hath Borne Our Griefs; Wir Eilen; Two Settings of a Poem by Rosaline; Festgesong an die Kunstler. Selections by the Friars: The Ballad of Little Musgrave and Lady Barnard; In His Care-O; Yonder Come Day; We've Only Just Begun; Spinning Wheel; Michigan Songs; Alma Mater.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club Seattle, Washington, 1973 May; 3 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-57-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 3; Men's Glee Club performance in Seattle Washington, no other information given.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-57-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 3; Men's Glee Club performance in Seattle Washington, no other information given.)
      - [Tape 3, Part 1], [87250-SR-57-3-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 3 of 3; Men's Glee Club performance in Seattle Washington, no other information given.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club & Morehouse College Fall Concert, 1973 November 09; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-58-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; The combined Glee Clubs perform: Come Peace of God. The Morehouse College Glee Club performs: Canticle of Peace; Salvation Belongeth to Our God; In the Midst of Silence; Roberta Lee; The Impossible Dream; Okradi; Betelehemu; Mary Had a Baby; Git on Board; Soon ah Will Be Done; If You Want to be Happy. Combined Glee Clubs perform: Vive L'Amour. The Michigan Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Inveni Davida; Hospodi Pomilui; Vocalise; To Revive a Chilled Pig; Selections by the Friars; Bouree; You've Got a Friend; Somebody Callin' My Name; My Soul's Been Anchored; Michigan Songs. The combined Glee Clubs perform: Amazin' Grace; Dear Old Morehouse; The Yellow and Blue.)
      - Tape 1, [Part 1], [87250-SR-58-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; The combined Glee Clubs perform: Come Peace of God. The Morehouse College Glee Club performs: Canticle of Peace; Salvation Belongeth to Our God; In the Midst of Silence; Roberta Lee; The Impossible Dream; Okradi; Betelehemu; Mary Had a Baby; Git on Board; Soon ah Will Be Done; If You Want to be Happy. Combined Glee Clubs perform: Vive L'Amour. The Michigan Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Inveni Davida; Hospodi Pomilui; Vocalise; To Revive a Chilled Pig; Selections by the Friars; Bouree; You've Got a Friend; Somebody Callin' My Name; My Soul's Been Anchored; Michigan Songs. The combined Glee Clubs perform: Amazin' Grace; Dear Old Morehouse; The Yellow and Blue.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 114th Annual Spring Concert, 1974 March 30; 3 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-59-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 3; The Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Let Nothing Ever Grieve Thee; Go Lovely Rose!; Red Iron Ore; Yonder! Yonder!; Drinking Song form Sir John in Love; Fugue in C Minor. A selection of songs by the Friars; This is All I ask; There is Nothin' Like a Dame; Negro Spirituals; I Want Jesus to Walk With Me; Set Down Servant; (Michigan Songs) Michigan Medley; Bum Army; Ann Arbor Days; Varsity; Victors; Yellow and Blue.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-59-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 3; The Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Let Nothing Ever Grieve Thee; Go Lovely Rose!; Red Iron Ore; Yonder! Yonder!; Drinking Song form Sir John in Love; Fugue in C Minor. A selection of songs by the Friars; This is All I ask; There is Nothin' Like a Dame; Negro Spirituals; I Want Jesus to Walk With Me; Set Down Servant; (Michigan Songs) Michigan Medley; Bum Army; Ann Arbor Days; Varsity; Victors; Yellow and Blue.)
      - [Tape 3, Part 1], [87250-SR-59-3-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 3 of 3; The Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Let Nothing Ever Grieve Thee; Go Lovely Rose!; Red Iron Ore; Yonder! Yonder!; Drinking Song form Sir John in Love; Fugue in C Minor. A selection of songs by the Friars; This is All I ask; There is Nothin' Like a Dame; Negro Spirituals; I Want Jesus to Walk With Me; Set Down Servant; (Michigan Songs) Michigan Medley; Bum Army; Ann Arbor Days; Varsity; Victors; Yellow and Blue.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club & Ohio State University 115th Fall Concert, 1974 November 16; 3 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-60-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 3; The Ohio State University Glee Club performs: Lift Up Your Heads, O Ye Gates; Gloria Patri; Kyrie Eleison; Shivisi; A New Heart Will I Give You; Coronation Scene; Hola Hi, Holla Ho!; Magdlein im Walde; Down In The Valley; Doctor Foster; When Johnny Comes Marching Home; A Lot of Livin'; Campus Echoes; Benediction.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-60-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 3; The Michigan Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Salvation Belongeth To Our God; A Thanksgiving To God For His House; The Lost Chord; Standchen; Boatmen's Dance; Shenandoah. Selections performed by the Friars.)
      - [Tape 3, Part 1], [87250-SR-60-3-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 3 of 3; The Michigan Glee Club performs: Geographical Fugue; Let Us Break Bread Together; In That New Jerusalem; Honey Brown; Michigan Songs.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club Christmas Recording, 1974; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-61-1-1]; mp3 file; (Reel 2 of 2; Reel 1 missing; Michigan Glee Club performs: O Come, O Come Emanuel; Patapan; Christmas Song; Behold That Star; O Tannenbaum; Silent Night; O Come All Ye Faithful; Twelve Days After Christmas; God Rest Ye Merry Gentlemen; O Holy Night; The Boars' Head Carol; I Wonde As I Wander; Winter Wonderland; Gesu Bambino; Carol of the Drums.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 115th Annual Spring Concert, 1975 April 12; 3 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-62-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 3; Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Adoramus Te, Christe; Emitte Spiritum tuum; Jesus and the Traders; (Three Villanellas) Throughout the World; When I Admire The Rose; John and His Father; Alto Rhapsody. Selections by The Friars. Zitti, Zitti from Rigoletto; Blossom; Old King Cole; Done Foun' My Los' Sheep; Jerry; Ain't a dat Good News; Michigan Songs.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-62-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 3; Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Adoramus Te, Christe; Emitte Spiritum tuum; Jesus and the Traders; (Three Villanellas) Throughout the World; When I Admire The Rose; John and His Father; Alto Rhapsody. Selections by The Friars. Zitti, Zitti from Rigoletto; Blossom; Old King Cole; Done Foun' My Los' Sheep; Jerry; Ain't a dat Good News; Michigan Songs.)
      - [Tape 3, Part 1], [87250-SR-62-3-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 3 of 3; Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Adoramus Te, Christe; Emitte Spiritum tuum; Jesus and the Traders; (Three Villanellas) Throughout the World; When I Admire The Rose; John and His Father; Alto Rhapsody. Selections by The Friars. Zitti, Zitti from Rigoletto; Blossom; Old King Cole; Done Foun' My Los' Sheep; Jerry; Ain't a dat Good News; Michigan Songs.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 115th Fall Joint Concert with Cornell, 1975 November 22; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-63-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; Cornell Glee Club performs: Psaume; Gesang der Geister uber den Wassern; Tarantella; Father William; Aj lucka siroka; La Banda; Su la Piu Alta Cima; I Gave Her Cakes and I Gave Her Ale; Once, Twice, Thrice I Julia tried; The Hangovers (selections); Cornell College Songs. Michigan Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Chester; When Jesus Wept; Amanda; Battle of Stonington; The Celestial Vision part 1; The Friars (selections); Lowlands; Poor Man Lazarus; Rainbow 'Round My Shoulder; Moon Indigo; Michigan Songs; The God Who Gave Us Life; I Shall Not Die Without a Hope. Alma Maters by Combined Glee Clubs: Far Above Cayuga's Water; Yellow and Blue.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1-1], [87250-SR-63-2-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; Cornell Glee Club performs: Psaume; Gesang der Geister uber den Wassern; Tarantella; Father William; Aj lucka siroka; La Banda; Su la Piu Alta Cima; I Gave Her Cakes and I Gave Her Ale; Once, Twice, Thrice I Julia tried; The Hangovers (selections); Cornell College Songs. Michigan Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Chester; When Jesus Wept; Amanda; Battle of Stonington; The Celestial Vision part 1; The Friars (selections); Lowlands; Poor Man Lazarus; Rainbow 'Round My Shoulder; Moon Indigo; Michigan Songs; The God Who Gave Us Life; I Shall Not Die Without a Hope. Alma Maters by Combined Glee Clubs: Far Above Cayuga's Water; Yellow and Blue.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1-2], [87250-SR-63-2-1-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; Cornell Glee Club performs: Psaume; Gesang der Geister uber den Wassern; Tarantella; Father William; Aj lucka siroka; La Banda; Su la Piu Alta Cima; I Gave Her Cakes and I Gave Her Ale; Once, Twice, Thrice I Julia tried; The Hangovers (selections); Cornell College Songs. Michigan Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Chester; When Jesus Wept; Amanda; Battle of Stonington; The Celestial Vision part 1; The Friars (selections); Lowlands; Poor Man Lazarus; Rainbow 'Round My Shoulder; Moon Indigo; Michigan Songs; The God Who Gave Us Life; I Shall Not Die Without a Hope. Alma Maters by Combined Glee Clubs: Far Above Cayuga's Water; Yellow and Blue.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 116th Annual Spring Concert, 1976 April 10; 3 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-64-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 3; The Men's Glee Club performs: The Star Spangled Banner; Laudes Atque Carmina; O Sing Unto the Lord; Laura Lee; If You've Only Got a Moustache; Come Where My Love Lies Dreaming; I Dream of Jeannie; Some Folks; The Pasture; I Hear an Army; Remember Me; Where You There?)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-64-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 3; The Friars perform: The Corn Huskers; We're Goin' Around; We Will Rest Awhile; Maple Leaf Rag; Three Preludes.)
      - [Tape 3, Part 1], [87250-SR-64-3-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 3 of 3; The Men's Glee Club performs: Circus Band; Waltz; In The Alley; Son of a Gambolier; Michigan Songs; Yellow and Blue.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 117th Fall Concert, 1976 November 13; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-65-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; Illinois Glee Club performs: Cry Out and Shout; Ave Maria; Salvation Belongeth To Ur God; Trosterin Musik; Sally Gardens; In Praise of Hunting; Daybreak; Drinking Song; Selections by The Other Guys: A Capital Ship; Black Is The Color of My True Love's Hair; The Battle of Jericho; People; Big Ten Medley)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1-1], [87250-SR-65-2-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; Michigan Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Exultate Deo; O Isis und Osiris; Chorus from the Priests; I'd Enter Your Garden; The Fiddler; How Sad Flow the Streams; The Last Words of David. Selections by the Friars: Is My Team Ploughing?; Ev'ry Time I Feel The Spirit; Try To Remember; Michigan Songs; Brothers, Sing On. Alma Maters by Combined Glee Clubs: Hail to the Orange; Yellow and Blue.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1-2], [87250-SR-65-2-1-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; Michigan Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Exultate Deo; O Isis und Osiris; Chorus from the Priests; I'd Enter Your Garden; The Fiddler; How Sad Flow the Streams; The Last Words of David. Selections by the Friars: Is My Team Ploughing?; Ev'ry Time I Feel The Spirit; Try To Remember; Michigan Songs; Brothers, Sing On. Alma Maters by Combined Glee Clubs: Hail to the Orange; Yellow and Blue.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club "Songs of Michigan" Pressing Master, 1977; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 15 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-66-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; The Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Tis of Michigan We Sing; A Toast to Michigan; I Want to Go Back To Michigan; Goddess of the Inland Sea; Go Blue; Michigan Men; I'll Ne'er Forget My College Days; The Friars Song; The University)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-66-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; The Men's Glee Club performs: The Hymn To Michigan; The Bum Army; In College Days; When Night Falls; Ann Arbor Days; Varsity; The Victors; Yellow and Blue.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 117th Annual Spring Concert, 1977 April 02; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-67-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; The Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Miserere Mei; Man is For The Woman Made; Lovers Love The Spring; Chorus of the Returning Pilgrims; Tarantella; Gaudeamus Igitur; Chanson a Boire; Drinking Song; The Faucet. Selections by the Friars: Processional; Inveni David; Spirituals. Selections by The Midnight Sons: Bachelor's Dance; Michigan Songs; The Yellow and Blue.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-67-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; The Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Miserere Mei; Man is For The Woman Made; Lovers Love The Spring; Chorus of the Returning Pilgrims; Tarantella; Gaudeamus Igitur; Chanson a Boire; Drinking Song; The Faucet. Selections by the Friars: Processional; Inveni David; Spirituals. Selections by The Midnight Sons: Bachelor's Dance; Michigan Songs; The Yellow and Blue.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 118th Fall Concert with The Arbors, 1977 November 19; 3 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-68-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 3; The Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Good Fellows, Be Merry; Evviva! Beviam!; Fac me vere; As Beautiful as She; Deep River; Set Down Servant! Selections by The Friars.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-68-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; The Men's Glee Club performs: A-Roving; The Boatmen's Dance; Night and Day; Scarborough Fair; Songs of the University of Michigan.)
      - [Tape 3, Part 1], [87250-SR-68-3-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 3 of 3; Selections by the Arbors: The Heart Worships; Varsity and the Victors; The Yellow and Blue.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 118th Annual Spring Concert, 1978 March 18; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-69-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; The Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Ascendit Deus; Psalm 23; Widerspruch; Salvation Is Created; Hospodi Pomilui; The Ballad of Little Musgrave and Lady Barnard; Lowlands; Old Mother Hubbard. Selections by the Friars: Joshua Fit De Battle ob Jericho; Swing dat Hammer!; Michigan Morn. Selections by the Midnight Suns: Cole Porter Medley; Michigan Songs; The Yellow and Blue.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-69-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; The Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Ascendit Deus; Psalm 23; Widerspruch; Salvation Is Created; Hospodi Pomilui; The Ballad of Little Musgrave and Lady Barnard; Lowlands; Old Mother Hubbard. Selections by the Friars: Joshua Fit De Battle ob Jericho; Swing dat Hammer!; Michigan Morn. Selections by the Midnight Suns: Cole Porter Medley; Michigan Songs; The Yellow and Blue.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club Vienna I & II, 1978; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 15 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1-1], [87250-SR-70-1-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; The Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Ascendit Deus; Salvation is Created; Hospodi Pomilui; When Jesus Wept; The Bridal Party; Where Shall The Lover Rest?; Chester; Laura Lee; Lowlands.)
      - [Tape 1, Part 1-2], [87250-SR-70-1-1-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; Tape content does not match original description; recording of solo piano)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1-2], [87250-SR-70-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; The Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Ascendit Deus; Salvation is Created; Hospodi Pomilui; When Jesus Wept; The Bridal Party; Where Shall The Lover Rest?; Chester; Laura Lee; Lowlands.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club St. Blasius, 1978; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 15 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-71-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; The Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Ascendit Deus; Gott Meine Zuversicht; Widerspruch; The Bridal Party; Where Shall the Lover Rest; Chester; Laura Lee; The Pasture; Lowlands; Stomp Your Foot.)
      - [Tape 1, Part 2], [87250-SR-71-1-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; Tape content does not match original description; test recording in German)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-71-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; Selections by The Friars: The When You and I Were Young Maggie Blues; The Sunshine Girl; Mamma Look Sharp; Little Darlin'. The Men's Glee Club performs: The Ballad of Little Musgrave and Lady Barnard; Remember Me; Deep River; Set Down Servant; Ev'ry Time; Cole Porter Medley; 'Tis of Michigan We Sing; Fill Your Tankards; Ann Arbor Days; The Yellow and Blue; Salvation is Created.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 119th Fall Concert & Purdue University Men's Glee Club, 1978 November 18; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch
      - [Tape 1, Part 1-1], [87250-SR-72-1-1-1]; mp3 file; (Part 1 of 2; Unlisted selections by the Purdue University Glee Club. Michigan Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Then Round About the Starry Throne; To The Women; The Llangollen Song; The Bridal Party; Where Shall the Lover Rest; Stomp Your Foot; The Friars (selections); Vive L'Amour; John Was a Writer; There Is a Balm in Gilead; Cockles and Mussels; Michigan Songs; Brothers Sing On. Alma Maters by the Combined Glee Clubs: Hail Purdue; The Yellow and Blue)
      - Tape 1, Part 1-2], [87250-SR-72-1-1-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; Unlisted selections by the Purdue University Glee Club. Michigan Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Then Round About the Starry Throne; To The Women; The Llangollen Song; The Bridal Party; Where Shall the Lover Rest; Stomp Your Foot; The Friars (selections); Vive L'Amour; John Was a Writer; There Is a Balm in Gilead; Cockles and Mussels; Michigan Songs; Brothers Sing On. Alma Maters by the Combined Glee Clubs: Hail Purdue; The Yellow and Blue)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-72-2-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; Unlisted selections by the Purdue University Glee Club. Michigan Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Then Round About the Starry Throne; To The Women; The Llangollen Song; The Bridal Party; Where Shall the Lover Rest; Stomp Your Foot; The Friars (selections); Vive L'Amour; John Was a Writer; There Is a Balm in Gilead; Cockles and Mussels; Michigan Songs; Brothers Sing On. Alma Maters by the Combined Glee Clubs: Hail Purdue; The Yellow and Blue)
      - [Tape 2, Part 2], [87250-SR-72-2-1-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; Unlisted selections by the Purdue University Glee Club. Michigan Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Then Round About the Starry Throne; To The Women; The Llangollen Song; The Bridal Party; Where Shall the Lover Rest; Stomp Your Foot; The Friars (selections); Vive L'Amour; John Was a Writer; There Is a Balm in Gilead; Cockles and Mussels; Michigan Songs; Brothers Sing On. Alma Maters by the Combined Glee Clubs: Hail Purdue; The Yellow and Blue)